ananthapuri.com 2003-10-12

# Ananthapuri.com » Privacy Policy

---  
  
|   
  
---  
| 

  1. Ananthapuri.com is sensitive to privacy issues on the Internet and is committed to safeguarding the privacy of user online. 
  2. Users should be aware that when they voluntarily disclose personal information on message boards or in the chat areas or guestbook, that information can be collected and used by others and may result in unsolicited messages from other parties. 
  3. Ananthapuri.com shall not reveal any personal information that users provide to us, to any third party without the users' permission, unless, Ananthapuri.com has a reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating the Terms of Use, or may be causing injury to, or interfering with the rights or property of itself, other users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. Ananthapuri.com may disclose or access account information when it believes in good faith that the law requires it and for administrative and other purposes that we deem necessary to maintain, service and improve our products and services. 
  4. Ananthapuri.com is not responsible for the privacy practices employed by advertisers or sites to which links are provided by Ananthapuri.com 
  5. Users are expected to stay on topic related to the area in which he/she is participating 
  6. Personal information is used to deliver targeted advertisements to the user according to the specifications of the advertiser. This does not imply that the advertiser or any third party has an access to user's personal information. They will only receive aggregated user statistics . Only Ananthapuri.com has access to Users' accounts. 
  7. Information provided by all Users needs to be true, accurate, current and complete as required by the registration form and promptly updated to keep it true, accurate, current and complete. The privacy policy covers exchanges of personally identifiable information within sites of Ananthapuri.com. If you have any questions or comments regarding your privacy at Ananthapuri.com, please e-mail us .
